Guide to the Clarence Prouty Shedd Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence, 1923-1967; Series I
  - Y.W. C.A. - National Student Council, 1931-1955 (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - Z, 1946, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 249)
- Writings, 1925-1966; Series II
  The second series is divided into three sections:
  Addresses and Lectures
  Articles
  Book Reviews
  The material within each section is organized chronologically, with titles noted. Dated material is followed by undated material.
  - Addresses and Lectures
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1930-1937 (Box 19, Folder 250)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1939-1945 (Box 19, Folder 251)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1946-1949 (Box 19, Folder 252)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1954-1956 Sep (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1956 Nov-1965 Dec (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1957 Jan-1957 May (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1957 Sep-1957 Dec (Box 20, Folder 258)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1957 n.m. (Box 20, Folder 259)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1958 Feb (Box 20, Folder 260)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1958 Mar-1958 n.m. (Box 20, Folder 261)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 262)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 263)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - Addresses and Lectures, 1961-1966 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Addresses and Lectures (Box 21, Folder 266)
    - Addresses and Lectures (Box 21, Folder 267)
    - Addresses and Lectures (Box 21, Folder 268)
  - Articles
    - "The Work of the Denominations ", 1925 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - "Education a Co-operative Adventure ", 1929 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - "Observations on the Present Work of the W.S.C.F. ", 1932 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - "Nationalism in European Student Movements", 1934 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - "David R. Porter ", 1935 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - "Religion in the Colleges ", 1940 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - "Religion in State Universities", 1941 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - "Education--but not as usual ", 1942 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - "Agencies of Religion in Higher Education ", 1943 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - "The Christian Movement among Students ", 1943 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - "War-Time Adjustments ", 1944 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - "A Century of Christian Student Initiative ", 1944 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - "A Time for Decision in Y.M.C.A.--Church Relations", 1945 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - "The Movements of Religion in American", 1945 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - "Higher Education Proposals for Religion in Postwar Higher Education" ", 1945 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - "Religion in the State University ", 1947 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - "Henri Dunant et le developpement international des Y.M.C.A. ", 1949 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - "Moral and Spiritual Values in Public H.E. ", 1953 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - "Religion in H.E.--Retrospect and Prospect ", 1955 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - "Higher Education in the U.S.", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - "Historical Notes on Teaching of Religion", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - "Hutchins' Philosophy of Education", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - "Influence of Religion on History of American H.E.", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - "The Movement and the Student Christian Associations " (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - "The Movements of Religion in American H.E.", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - "Priorities for the Christian Movement in War-Times", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - "The Problem of Suffering in the Old Testament ", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - "Religion in American Higher Education", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - "Religion in Post-War Higher Education", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - "Religion in the Colleges ", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - "Religious Program for Smaller Church- Related and Private Colleges Having Military Units" (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - "Student Religious Organizations The Student Y.M.C.A. in the World's Alliance History", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 277)
    - Fragments, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - Book Reviews
    - Various, 1922-1950 (Box 22, Folder 278)
- Source Material, 1920s-1940s; Series III
  The material in Series III is organized alphabetically by topic. In most cases the material is not in chronological order within each topic.
  - Academic Freedom (Box 23, Folder 279)
  - Administrative Responsibility (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Administrative Responsibility (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Aims of Higher Education (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - American Colleges (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Asia - Student Work (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Buchmanism (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Campus Christian Ministry (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Campus Religious Life: Butler Study, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Campus Religious Life: Butler Study, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Campus Religious Life: Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Catholic Higher Education and Student Work (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Catholics and the Y.M.C.A. (Box 24, Folder 292)
  - Centennial Conference Committee, Paris,1953 (Box 24, Folder 292a)
  - Chaplaincy (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Christian World Education (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - The Church Follows its Students (CFS): Church Student Work (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - CFS: Church Student Work (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - CFS: Church work in state university (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - CFS: The Church worker's program (Chapter 5) (Box 25, Folder 298)
  - CFS: College authorities' conceptions of university pastorates (Box 25, Folder 299)
  - CFS: Congregational student work (Box 25, Folder 300)
  - CFS: Correspondence with denominational boards (Box 25, Folder 301)
  - CFS: Correspondence with denominational boards (Box 25, Folder 302)
  - CFS: Correspondence with denominational boards (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - CFS: Correspondence regarding publication and publicity (Box 25, Folder 304)
  - CFS: Correspondence regarding publication and publicity (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - CFS: Disciples of Christ student work (Box 26, Folder 306)
  - CFS: Financing church student work (Box 26, Folder 307)
  - CFS: Foreword and Footnotes (Box 26, Folder 308)
  - CFS: Future problems of church student work (Chapter 8) (Box 26, Folder 309)
  - CFS: Interdenominational cooperation (Box 26, Folder 310)
  - CFS: Interdenominational cooperation (Box 26, Folder 311)
  - CFS: Lists of church workers with students (Box 26, Folder 312)
  - CFS: Methodist student work (Box 26, Folder 313)
  - CFS: Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 26, Folder 314)
  - CFS: Northern Baptist student work (Box 26, Folder 315)
  - CFS: The organization of the denominational university pastorate (Chapter 4) (Box 26, Folder 316)
  - CFS: Personnel study of the university pastorate (Box 27, Folder 317)
  - CFS: Philosophy of the student pastorate (Box 27, Folder 318)
  - CFS: Preliminary study (1932): Church Workers in State and Larger Independent Universities in the U.S.A. (Box 27, Folder 319)
  - CFS: Presbyterian student work (Box 27, Folder 320)
  - CFS: Presbyterian (U.S.) student work (Box 27, Folder 321)
  - CFS: Presbyterian (U.S.A.) student work (Box 27, Folder 322)
  - CFS: Protestant Episcopal student work (Box 27, Folder 323)
  - CFS: Questionnaires (Box 28, Folder 324)
  - CFS: Questionnaires (Box 28, Folder 325)
  - CFS: Questionnaires (Box 28, Folder 326)
  - CFS: Questionnaires (Box 28, Folder 327)
  - CFS: Questionnaires (Box 28, Folder 328)
  - CFS: Quotations from local student pastors' reports (Box 28, Folder 329)
  - CFS: Reviews and comments regarding the book (Box 29, Folder 330)
  - CFS: The Rise of the Big University (intended Chapter 1) (Box 29, Folder 331)
  - CFS: Roman Catholic student work (Box 29, Folder 332)
  - CFS: The second decade, 1910-1920 (Chapter 2) (Box 29, Folder 333)
  - CFS: Shedd: B.D. thesis: The Church at Work with Students (Box 29, Folder 334)
  - CFS: Summaries of replies to questionnaires (Box 29, Folder 335)
  - CFS: Summaries of replies to questionnaires (Box 29, Folder 336)
  - CFS: Typescript draft pp. 1-152 (Box 30, Folder 337)
  - CFS: Typescript draft pp. 153-end (Box 30, Folder 338)
  - CFS: Unitarian student work (Box 30, Folder 339)
  - CFS: The university pastorate as seen by church workers (Chapter 8) (Box 30, Folder 340)
  - CFS: The vocational opportunity in the university pastorate (Chapter 6) (Box 30, Folder 341)
  - CFS: Women's student work (Box 30, Folder 342)
  - Church-Related Colleges (Box 30, Folder 343)
  - Church School Youth Work (Box 30, Folder 344)
  - Church Student Work (Box 30, Folder 345)
  - Church Student Work (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 348)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 31, Folder 351)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 31, Folder 352)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Interdollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 31, Folder 353)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 32, Folder 354)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 32, Folder 355)
  - Church-Student Work Relationships: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Study (Box 32, Folder 356)
  - Churchmanship (Box 32, Folder 357)
  - College Chapels and Student Religious Centers (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - The College Teacher and Student Religion - Espy Study (CTSR): Comments supplementing questionnaire (Box 33, Folder 359)
  - CTSR: Correlations (Box 33, Folder 360)
  - CTSR: Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 361)
  - CTSR: Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 362)
  - CTSR: Formulations of Project (Box 33, Folder 363)
  - CTSR: Material regarding questionnaire (Box 33, Folder 364)
  - CTSR: Questionnaires (Box 34, Folder 365)
  - CTSR: Questionnaires (Box 35, Folder 366)
  - CTSR: Questionnaires (Box 36, Folder 366a)
  - CTSR: Questionnaires (Box 37, Folder 367)
  - CTSR: Questionnaires - drafts (Box 38, Folder 368)
  - CTSR: Selection of Participants (Box 38, Folder 369)
  - CTSR: Shedd's Notes (Box 38, Folder 370)
  - Congregational Christian Churches: Student Work (Box 38, Folder 371)
  - Consultative Trips of Shedd: Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 372)
  - Consultative Trips of Shedd: Pacific Coast Trip, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 373)
  - Consultative Trips of Shedd: Southern Trip, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 374)
  - Counseling (Box 38, Folder 375)
  - Counseling (Box 38, Folder 376)
  - Davis, Jerome - Case at Yale (Box 39, Folder 377)
  - Denominational Student Programs (Box 39, Folder 378)
  - Disciples of Christ Student Work (Box 39, Folder 379)
  - Ecumenism (Box 39, Folder 380)
  - Enrollment Trends in Higher Education (Box 39, Folder 381)
  - Espy, R.H. Edwin (Box 39, Folder 382)
  - European American Associations (Box 39, Folder 383)
  - European Universities (Box 39, Folder 384)
  - Evangelism (Box 39, Folder 385)
  - Evangelism (Box 39, Folder 386)
  - Experimentation in Higher Education (Box 40, Folder 387)
  - Extra-Curricular Activities (Box 40, Folder 388)
  - Faculty Christian Fellowship (Box 40, Folder 389)
  - Faculty Conferences (Box 40, Folder 390)
  - Faculty Religious Influence (Box 40, Folder 391)
  - Faculty-Student Relationships (Box 40, Folder 392)
  - Foreign Students (Box 40, Folder 393)
  - Fraternities (Box 40, Folder 394)
  - Freshman Camps (Box 40, Folder 395)
  - Freshman Student Work (Box 41, Folder 396)
  - Freshman Student Work (Box 41, Folder 397)
  - General Education (Box 41, Folder 398)
  - Group Work (Box 41, Folder 399)
  - History of Higher Education (Box 41, Folder 400)
  - History of Student Christian Movement (Box 41, Folder 401)
  - History of Student Christian Movement (Box 41, Folder 402)
  - History of Student Christian Movement (Box 41, Folder 403)
  - History of Student Christian Movement (Box 41, Folder 404)
  - History of Student Christian Movement in Colleges - (Card file) (Box 42, Folder 405)
  - History of the World's Alliance of Y.M.C.A.'s (HWAY): Card File (Box 43, Folder 406)
  - HWAY: Card File (Box 44, Folder 407)
  - HWAY: Centennial in Paris, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 408)
  - HWAY: Centennial in Paris, 1955 - Notes for speech (Box 45, Folder 409)
  - HWAY: Consultation on Student Work, Bievres, France, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 410)
  - HWAY: Correspondence with Paul Limbert (Box 45, Folder 411)
  - HWAY: Correspondence with Sir Frank Willis (Box 45, Folder 412)
  - HWAY: Foreword (Box 45, Folder 413)
  - HWAY: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 414)
  - HWAY: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 415)
  - HWAY: Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 46, Folder 416)
  - HWAY: Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 46, Folder 417)
  - HWAY: Miscellaneous notes (Box 46, Folder 418)
  - HWAY: Notes regarding Karl Fries (Box 46, Folder 419)
  - HWAY: Notes regarding John R. Mott (Box 46, Folder 420)
  - HWAY: Plenary meeting, Geneva, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 421)
  - HWAY: References and reviews (Box 46, Folder 422)
  - HWAY: Chapter 1 (Box 46, Folder 423)
  - HWAY: Chapter 2 (Box 46, Folder 424)
  - HWAY: Chapter 3 (Box 46, Folder 425)
  - HWAY: Chapter 4 (Box 46, Folder 426)
  - HWAY: Chapter 5 (Box 47, Folder 427)
  - HWAY: Chapter 6 (Box 47, Folder 428)
  - HWAY: Chapters 7, 8 (Box 47, Folder 429)
  - HWAY: Chapters 7, 8 (Box 47, Folder 430)
  - HWAY: Chapter 9 (Box 47, Folder 431)
  - HWAY: Chapter 10 (Box 47, Folder 432)
  - HWAY: Chapter 11 (Box 47, Folder 433)
  - Honor System (Box 48, Folder 434)
  - Hutchins, Robert J. (Box 48, Folder 435)
  - Interfaith Cooperation (Box 48, Folder 436)
  - Interfaith Cooperation (Box 48, Folder 437)
  - International Understanding (Box 48, Folder 438)
  - Interseminary Movement in the U.S. (Box 48, Folder 439)
  - Issues in Religion in Higher Education, 1930-1940 (card file) (Box 49, Folder 440)
  - Jewish Student Work (Box 50, Folder 441)
  - Junior Colleges (Box 50, Folder 442)
  - Leadership in Student Christian Associations (Box 50, Folder 443)
  - Lutheran Student Work (Box 50, Folder 444)
  - Methodist Student Work (Box 50, Folder 445)
  - Methodist Student Work (Box 50, Folder 446)
  - Moberly, Sir Walter; The Crisis in the University (Box 50, Folder 447)
  - National Commission on Consultations about Student Christian Work (NCCSCW): Administrative Committee (Box 50, Folder 448)
  - NCCSCW: Central Field (Box 50, Folder 449)
  - NCCSCW: Committee on Message and Task (Box 50, Folder 450)
  - NCCSCW: Committee on Structure (Box 50, Folder 451)
  - NCCSCW: Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 452)
  - NCCSCW: Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 453)
  - NCCSCW: Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 454)
  - NCCSCW: Mailing Lists (Box 51, Folder 455)
  - NCCSCW: Middle Atlantic Field (Box 51, Folder 456)
  - NCCSCW: Minutes, reports (Box 51, Folder 457)
  - NCCSCW: New England Field (Box 51, Folder 458)
  - NCCSCW: Pacific Coast Field (Box 51, Folder 459)
  - NCCSCW: Place and Function Committee (Box 51, Folder 460)
  - NCCSCW: Rocky Mountain Field (Box 51, Folder 461)
  - NCCSCW: Southern Fields (Box 51, Folder 462)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council (Box 51, Folder 463)
  - National Student Christian Federation: Student-Faculty Conference, Detroit, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 464)
  - NSCF Conference: Commission VII - The Place of Religion and Religious Agencies in Student Life Today (Box 51, Folder 465)
  - NSCF Conference: Commission VII - The Place of Religion and Religious Activities in Student Life Today (Box 51, Folder 466)
  - NSCF Conference: Commission Outlines (Box 51, Folder 467)
  - NSCF Conference: Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 468)
  - NSCF Conference: Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 469)
  - NSCF Conference: Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 470)
  - NSCF Conference: Reports from colleges and universities (Box 52, Folder 471)
  - NSCF Conference: Reports from colleges and universities (Box 52, Folder 472)
  - Negroes and the Student Christian Movement (Box 52, Folder 473)
  - Northern Baptist Convention Student Work (Box 52, Folder 474)
  - Pangborn, Cyrus R. - R.H.E. Study, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 475)
  - Politics in the Student Christian Movement (Box 52, Folder 476)
  - Preparatory Schools (Box 52, Folder 477)
  - Presbyterian Church, U.S.; Student Work (Box 53, Folder 478)
  - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.; Student Work (Box 53, Folder 479)
  - Professional Problems and Relationships (Box 53, Folder 480)
  - Professional Training of Student Workers: United Student Christian Council Study (Box 53, Folder 481)
  - Professional Training of Student Workers: U. S. C. C. Study (Box 53, Folder 482)
  - Professional Training of Student Workers: U. S. C. C. Study (Box 53, Folder 483)
  - Professional Training of Student Workers: U. S. C. C. Study (Box 53, Folder 484)
  - Program Areas and Principles (Box 53, Folder 485)
  - Proposals for Reorganization of Higher Education (Box 54, Folder 486)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church; Student Work (Box 54, Folder 187)
  - Pursuit of Excellence (Box 54, Folder 488)
  - Questionnaires - Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 489)
  - Questionnaires - Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 490)
  - Race Relations (Box 54, Folder 491)
  - Relation of Men and Women in Student Christian Association Work (Box 54, Folder 492)
  - Religion and Public Education (Box 54, Folder 493)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 494)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 495)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Bibliographies and course descriptions (Box 55, Folder 496)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Bibliographies and course descriptions (Box 55, Folder 497)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Bibliographies and course descriptions (Box 55, Folder 498)
  - Religion in Higher Education: Bibliographies and course descriptions (Box 55, Folder 499)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Agee - Erpestad (Box 56, Folder 500)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Espy - Garwood (Box 56, Folder 501)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Glazier - Knoff (Box 56, Folder 502)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Landram - McKinney (Box 56, Folder 503)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Menke - Miller (Box 56, Folder 504)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: Rugh - Young (Box 56, Folder 505)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program Dissertation proposals, Shedd's notes: General and Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 506)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Funding records (Box 57, Folder 507)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 508)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Shedd course assignments (Box 57, Folder 509)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Shedd course commission topics (Box 57, Folder 510)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Shedd course examinations (Box 57, Folder 511)
  - Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program: Shedd course notes (Box 57, Folder 512)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: 1955 Conference (Box 57, Folder 513)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: Michaelson study (Box 57, Folder 514)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: Study of 1955, Correspondence with administrators (Box 57, Folder 515)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: Study of 1955, Correspondence with clergymen (Box 57, Folder 516)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: Study of 1955, Dallas Conference (Box 58, Folder 517)
  - Religion in Junior Colleges: Study of 1955, Mailing Lists (Box 58, Folder 518)
  - Religion in State Teachers' Colleges (Box 58, Folder 519)
  - Religion in State Teachers' Colleges (Box 58, Folder 520)
  - Religion in State Teachers' Colleges (Box 58, Folder 521)
  - Religion in State Teachers' Colleges (Box 58, Folder 522)
  - Religion in State Universities (RSU): Administrative Attitudes (Box 58, Folder 523)
  - RSU: Early documents, 1915, 1916 (Box 58, Folder 524)
  - RSU: Legal questions (Box 59, Folder 525)
  - RSU: Legal questions (Box 59, Folder 526)
  - RSU: Legal questions (Box 59, Folder 527)
  - RSU: Legal questions (Box 59, Folder 528)
  - RSU: Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 529)
  - RSU: Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 530)
  - RSU: Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 531)
  - RSU: Shedd trips, 1941, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 532)
  - RSU: Studies by others (Box 60, Folder 533)
  - RSU: Studies by others (Box 60, Folder 534)
  - RSU: Studies by others (Box 60, Folder 535)
  - RSU: Studies by Shedd (Box 60, Folder 536)
  - RSU: Alabama, University of (Box 61, Folder 537)
  - RSU: Alaska, University of (Box 61, Folder 538)
  - RSU: Alfred University (Box 61, Folder 539)
  - RSU: Arizona, University of (Box 61, Folder 540)
  - RSU: Arkansas State Teachers College (Box 61, Folder 541)
  - RSU: Arkansas, University of (Box 61, Folder 542)
  - RSU: Auburn University (Alabama) (Box 61, Folder 543)
  - RSU: Bishop College/Wiley College (Box 61, Folder 544)
  - RSU: California Institute of Technology (Box 61, Folder 545)
  - RSU: California, University of (Berkeley) (Box 61, Folder 546)
  - RSU: California, University of (Davis) (Box 61, Folder 547)
  - RSU: California, University of (Los Angeles) (Box 61, Folder 548)
  - RSU: California, University of (Riverside) (Box 61, Folder 549)
  - RSU: California, University of (Santa Barbara) (Box 61, Folder 550)
  - RSU: California, University of Southern (Box 61, Folder 551)
  - RSU: Clemson College (Box 61, Folder 552)
  - RSU: Colorado, University of (Box 61, Folder 553)
  - RSU: Connecticut, University of (Box 61, Folder 554)
  - RSU: Cornell University (Box 61, Folder 555)
  - RSU: Davidson College (Box 61, Folder 556)
  - RSU: Delaware, University of (Box 61, Folder 557)
  - RSU: Dubuque, University of (Box 61, Folder 558)
  - RSU: Evansville College (Box 61, Folder 559)
  - RSU: Florida State University (Box 62, Folder 560)
  - RSU: Florida, University of (Box 62, Folder 561)
  - RSU: Florida, University of (Box 62, Folder 562)
  - RSU: Fresno State College (Box 62, Folder 563)
  - RSU: Georgia Institute of Technology (Box 62, Folder 564)
  - RSU: Georgia State College for Women (Box 62, Folder 565)
  - RSU: Georgia, University of (Box 62, Folder 566)
  - RSU: Hawaii, University of (Box 62, Folder 567)
  - RSU: Houston, University of Howard University (Box 62, Folder 568)
  - RSU: Idaho, University of (Box 62, Folder 569)
  - RSU: Illinois, University of (Box 62, Folder 570)
  - RSU: Illinois, University of (Box 62, Folder 571)
  - RSU: Illinois, University of (Box 62, Folder 572)
  - RSU: Illinois, University of (Box 62, Folder 573)
  - RSU: Illinois, University of (Box 62, Folder 574)
  - RSU: Indiana, University of (Box 63, Folder 575)
  - RSU: Indiana, University of (Box 63, Folder 576)
  - RSU: Iowa State College (Ames) (Box 63, Folder 577)
  - RSU: Iowa State Teachers College (Cedar Falls) (Box 63, Folder 578)
  - RSU: Iowa, University of (Iowa City) (Box 63, Folder 579)
  - RSU: Iowa, University of (Iowa City) (Box 63, Folder 580)
  - RSU: Kansas State University (Box 63, Folder 581)
  - RSU: Kansas, University of (Box 63, Folder 582)
  - RSU: Kent State University (Box 63, Folder 583)
  - RSU: Kentucky, University of (Box 63, Folder 584)
  - RSU: Louisiana State University (Box 64, Folder 585)